{
  "1": {
    "question": "4513211345312225424323453",
    "answer": "wwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "2": {
    "question": "2212412245514233421141351",
    "answer": "bwwbwwbwwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "3": {
    "question": "1134343321112331415332425",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwbwwwbwwbbwwwwwwwbw",
    "size": 5
  },
  "4": {
    "question": "3714151265712374812366474732655132672148184572453138272673841475",
    "answer": "wbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbw",
    "size": 8
  },
  "5": {
    "question": "2481776576215183871522456877153251451278356283342431455117586466",
    "answer": "bwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "6": {
    "question": "262442456213312434522331435624244146",
    "answer": "bwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwbw",
    "size": 6
  },
  "7": {
    "question": "2416423616778523322576751524133854637412573252118271345647524184",
    "answer": "wbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "8": {
    "question": "5442733148665737214367585718241771547876657142228367742571158243",
    "answer": "bwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwbbwwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwww",
    "size": 8
  },
  "9": {
    "question": "3145121551454231223552341",
    "answer": "wwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "10": {
    "question": "2737261168713552138626742654523137454187624667237312562847231855",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwwbbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "11": {
    "question": "5423234521144333531223135",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwbw",
    "size": 5
  },
  "12": {
    "question": "5717613383457142753415562747568517283364212318574672835133841445",
    "answer": "wbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwwwwbwbwwbw",
    "size": 8
  },
  "13": {
    "question": "1862435137163282837471455211274321374516755313686235781255223671",
    "answer": "wwwbwwwbbwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwwwwbbwbwbwww",
    "size": 8
  },
  "14": {
    "question": "2135152333152434142443312",
    "answer": "wbwwwwwbwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "15": {
    "question": "255153546321251634213234324536155462",
    "answer": "bwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "16": {
    "question": "1353125431132253413253214",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwbwww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "17": {
    "question": "5863465477361845665284733564276177255414766243372147535813186161",
    "answer": "wwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbbwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "18": {
    "question": "4325434345215343521212133",
    "answer": "wwwwbbwwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwwbw",
    "size": 5
  },
  "19": {
    "question": "8265123465322741347685711153162556264787234351647821365652536823",
    "answer": "wbwwwwwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbw",
    "size": 8
  },
  "20": {
    "question": "7662352144185732135742483764742582455467487353435477161377238455",
    "answer": "wwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "21": {
    "question": "143121461352245451242513314225124236",
    "answer": "wbwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwwbww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "22": {
    "question": "632324524361326244544643463512231533",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "23": {
    "question": "1325234112453435243133212",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "24": {
    "question": "1643385273625176476526352558347772718516565712187825574385166327",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "25": {
    "question": "4331212341351141225221432",
    "answer": "wwbwbbwwwwwwwbwwbwwbbwwww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "26": {
    "question": "1163474235251834715863265451261331446287821411164372876522166456",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "27": {
    "question": "4152123414442312215215242",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "28": {
    "question": "322314156534541132212453362521331444",
    "answer": "bwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "29": {
    "question": "3215437627615285137465583467516747643512654316215165664378562135",
    "answer": "wwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwbbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "30": {
    "question": "4832421231358723728113752358764174155535874215631251645865243437",
    "answer": "bwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbw",
    "size": 8
  },
  "31": {
    "question": "445334132564346432254213544631523246",
    "answer": "wbwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwwbww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "32": {
    "question": "1424523154543131234332423",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "33": {
    "question": "5423242313154214134234454",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwbwwwwwwbbwwwwwwbwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "34": {
    "question": "361445625221154623352211413522324154",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwbwww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "35": {
    "question": "4353221243352223232424135",
    "answer": "wwwbwbwwwwwwbwbbwwbwwwwww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "36": {
    "question": "6185463762581277514637288465513642752366165752647354851267124842",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "37": {
    "question": "2762551154318627218327468674717221684416387742651276638323161548",
    "answer": "bwbwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwbbwbwwbww",
    "size": 8
  },
  "38": {
    "question": "3422142413153424323523113",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwwwwbwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "39": {
    "question": "3212124213432541343531334",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwbw",
    "size": 5
  },
  "40": {
    "question": "461522346231532612651243154456215265",
    "answer": "wwbwwbbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "41": {
    "question": "122463611322464215463516325144534653",
    "answer": "wbwwwwwwbwwbbwwwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "42": {
    "question": "3513453441345111321341324",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "43": {
    "question": "4112252313314531314114215",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwbwwwwwwbbwbwwwwwbw",
    "size": 5
  },
  "44": {
    "question": "244315562421424153315461253342431322",
    "answer": "wbwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbbwbwwwwwwbwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "45": {
    "question": "7485644343567615657132843168274782276353283614743741586242637736",
    "answer": "wbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbw",
    "size": 8
  },
  "46": {
    "question": "152414143126515334531343624135452455",
    "answer": "bwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "47": {
    "question": "1531412133541423451113252",
    "answer": "bwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "48": {
    "question": "2253431141341231343222415",
    "answer": "wbwwwwwbwbbwwwwwwwbwbwbww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "49": {
    "question": "431416144135513264451145346551435311",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "50": {
    "question": "345436651442523214532614123563516434",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "51": {
    "question": "6515575814276865571844262431542786641253434775217125464732568172",
    "answer": "wbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwww",
    "size": 8
  },
  "52": {
    "question": "6287217125467351517233481376562516148253823342761753611238374567",
    "answer": "wbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "53": {
    "question": "2243131243124352512424452",
    "answer": "bwbwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwbwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "54": {
    "question": "642653641312136425654313513231325162",
    "answer": "bwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "55": {
    "question": "3623531446763861631765482115672324671436843174253151817667834614",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbw",
    "size": 8
  },
  "56": {
    "question": "243153516223221542363115135642251434",
    "answer": "bwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbbwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "57": {
    "question": "231652251143652555365421424465541212",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "58": {
    "question": "4132353144243111123433411",
    "answer": "wwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "59": {
    "question": "5244144123343422351321445",
    "answer": "wwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbbwbww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "60": {
    "question": "561452552443453165614532534544145321",
    "answer": "bwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "61": {
    "question": "162625635142521624526514443656254314",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbbwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "62": {
    "question": "3512167866234184653148452351757313748226517836274815673327762441",
    "answer": "wwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwwwwbbwbwwbww",
    "size": 8
  },
  "63": {
    "question": "2132514152531142512312531",
    "answer": "wwwbwbwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "64": {
    "question": "1413241421214315321442144",
    "answer": "bwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "65": {
    "question": "1352141213134455243114253",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "66": {
    "question": "154256561424412465353124622541341623",
    "answer": "wbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbw",
    "size": 6
  },
  "67": {
    "question": "3633445541773825671156527462218262547238444587628323174678216271",
    "answer": "bwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "68": {
    "question": "4145152124354112132533541",
    "answer": "wwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "69": {
    "question": "632234154622532166331162263415421343",
    "answer": "wbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "70": {
    "question": "434654514264635431552116365242226413",
    "answer": "bwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbbwwbww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "71": {
    "question": "5341441315233521523433511",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbw",
    "size": 5
  },
  "72": {
    "question": "3648212681324576543583153725546456861624452376826874123145516843",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwwbwwwwbw",
    "size": 8
  },
  "73": {
    "question": "153542611334344156426515464534521461",
    "answer": "wwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "74": {
    "question": "5817526161332554617564387284142635727541422186726642522714463783",
    "answer": "wwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "75": {
    "question": "153154532316261531316241445532422652",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwwwbbwwbwwwwbwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "76": {
    "question": "4837526731122836334866577524647867142583826347174446347215758374",
    "answer": "wwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwwwwbbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbw",
    "size": 8
  },
  "77": {
    "question": "2675171215486773434274512175544318412547741653252714133232564176",
    "answer": "bwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbw",
    "size": 8
  },
  "78": {
    "question": "1212414542341241523121152",
    "answer": "bwwbwwbwwwwwbwbbwwwwwwbwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "79": {
    "question": "2411453421132133431441452",
    "answer": "wbwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "80": {
    "question": "6165213734171688783451448413637224544846576483212526478346681213",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "81": {
    "question": "2512124154324325331431342",
    "answer": "bwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "82": {
    "question": "145421235541456142164214321364254352",
    "answer": "wwwbwbbwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "83": {
    "question": "5236647843135225568573141318454282723765373661836521874748117652",
    "answer": "wwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbbwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "84": {
    "question": "133165512634553146623412346431461312",
    "answer": "bwbwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbbwwbwwwwwwbw",
    "size": 6
  },
  "85": {
    "question": "611532513236221354165123354112253615",
    "answer": "wbwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "86": {
    "question": "4421332411412353334121354",
    "answer": "bwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "87": {
    "question": "162543345312415331231644514426426112",
    "answer": "wwwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "88": {
    "question": "1225224533321423134445431",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "89": {
    "question": "4324121243431321432142214",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwbbwbww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "90": {
    "question": "1342121541321343415245431",
    "answer": "bwbwwwwwwbbwwbwwwbwwbwwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "91": {
    "question": "142123253654164552251546315465446251",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbw",
    "size": 6
  },
  "92": {
    "question": "4522321433321414413223315",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "93": {
    "question": "7561458647564422211478355567171412473153811265472372511264853171",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "94": {
    "question": "315326534544243615553334524531564251",
    "answer": "wwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "95": {
    "question": "1552232153445212153543211",
    "answer": "wwbwbbwwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "96": {
    "question": "566424255326124653613524512165356231",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwwbw",
    "size": 6
  },
  "97": {
    "question": "452164316235633541511426262211325615",
    "answer": "wwwwwbbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "98": {
    "question": "4617837627751384142166727166424553624817384455663648742133742132",
    "answer": "wbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbw",
    "size": 8
  },
  "99": {
    "question": "241526163522454531225365436615226113",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbw",
    "size": 6
  },
  "100": {
    "question": "2225465365827314475228577823655535413728876435765728453213158245",
    "answer": "bwbwbwbwwwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbbwwbwwww",
    "size": 8
  },
  "101": {
    "question": "2158536671162568151783363282271558732624572133834631587287647151",
    "answer": "wwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "102": {
    "question": "431636526142253665153632235211644351",
    "answer": "wbwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "103": {
    "question": "1683662747662854363482355347168134764538652474342331524632563154",
    "answer": "wbwwwbwwwwwbwwwbbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbw",
    "size": 8
  },
  "104": {
    "question": "5228466278712654228513473672537565723866446386128413723521571785",
    "answer": "wbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "105": {
    "question": "3531253534144255323142154",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "106": {
    "question": "8713632142711841752134282642738311524237412827453447561626643571",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "107": {
    "question": "3761325585451652661475724528631311365426211636425682573124532562",
    "answer": "wwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "108": {
    "question": "321565221435465311526423132451552441",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwbbwwbww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "109": {
    "question": "2241674771283534285225363764562144752258446261136513544224411385",
    "answer": "bwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwww",
    "size": 8
  },
  "110": {
    "question": "2245243155322431453254224",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbw",
    "size": 5
  },
  "111": {
    "question": "8316125476651426312548655318243248632574243561375472771852718145",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "112": {
    "question": "545462415233232541234546153624225443",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwwbwwbbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwbw",
    "size": 6
  },
  "113": {
    "question": "554136624321446512513654464155341625",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwbww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "114": {
    "question": "212315323154235261213266154623261233",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "115": {
    "question": "1143451243345443312445412",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "116": {
    "question": "4434525341435113235443423",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "117": {
    "question": "5242212534322414345135121",
    "answer": "wbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "118": {
    "question": "5663744353685421315343636457813578361574334511181574248344843266",
    "answer": "bwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbw",
    "size": 8
  },
  "119": {
    "question": "452623336354654531165324231163323146",
    "answer": "wwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwbbwwwww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "120": {
    "question": "255135346321261235255346611432334614",
    "answer": "bwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "121": {
    "question": "1872146371532477674812512611783772847775456781261757471254116357",
    "answer": "wwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwbbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbw",
    "size": 8
  },
  "122": {
    "question": "8155273473263348673454224867225642538673563813751472443353417662",
    "answer": "wwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwbbwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbww",
    "size": 8
  },
  "123": {
    "question": "5214132524214234213525324",
    "answer": "wwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbw",
    "size": 5
  },
  "124": {
    "question": "364114115432523314451216442363253645",
    "answer": "wwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "125": {
    "question": "145162544331312516154424331452464211",
    "answer": "bwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbbwwbwwwwbwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "126": {
    "question": "1341115442325114411311235",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "127": {
    "question": "2144525122431212423352114",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "128": {
    "question": "7364261824753831351183623265611368271526143832374182637525425481",
    "answer": "wwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "129": {
    "question": "1242112354245231543231241",
    "answer": "bwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "130": {
    "question": "2135223541151255234335212",
    "answer": "bwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "131": {
    "question": "2135125231544122214114223",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "132": {
    "question": "5312334245133544321425433",
    "answer": "wbwwwwwwbwwbwwbbwbwwwwwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "133": {
    "question": "325613153224243513361412113265234354",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "134": {
    "question": "8372426561343815575381361635287812867311254576317168172338776843",
    "answer": "wwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "135": {
    "question": "123126546432213615534421162353451464",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwwbbwwbww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "136": {
    "question": "1544441425511342351341231",
    "answer": "wwbwbbwwwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "137": {
    "question": "4118533246442541154762432774666572113584634548635431762877258476",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbw",
    "size": 8
  },
  "138": {
    "question": "3245812673345271651875375462787422413755862375141357468231715542",
    "answer": "wbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "139": {
    "question": "4453324125214525232115234",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwwwbw",
    "size": 5
  },
  "140": {
    "question": "4342334154211331434545212",
    "answer": "bwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "141": {
    "question": "4212511123143323524113111",
    "answer": "wwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "142": {
    "question": "112453434512231335446221354156125324",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwwwbw",
    "size": 6
  },
  "143": {
    "question": "165232631125543111121526211453142334",
    "answer": "bwwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbw",
    "size": 6
  },
  "144": {
    "question": "1123442115354111454234134",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "145": {
    "question": "3641158683226752186342152145816446267118643258765663272114585643",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwwwbwwbwbbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwww",
    "size": 8
  },
  "146": {
    "question": "2476325172244566182564573635733433478126631217354736284341833672",
    "answer": "bwwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwww",
    "size": 8
  },
  "147": {
    "question": "7413653111365327653821751762327812822456287411658715472532678614",
    "answer": "wwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwbbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwww",
    "size": 8
  },
  "148": {
    "question": "5313143511453141235311145",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwwbbwbww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "149": {
    "question": "165233523452624153333513251245156322",
    "answer": "bwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "150": {
    "question": "2214275777538526145743863248561726873451135112464832657517214835",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "151": {
    "question": "8557164343524111181475266426335577635235218344273277186476518377",
    "answer": "wwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "152": {
    "question": "511521134226561445452362326143245331",
    "answer": "bwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "153": {
    "question": "3625287551613182247845156246213434126753654723251523263778365764",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "154": {
    "question": "351144612521134654461434415163524213",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "155": {
    "question": "2782254555348521235174851465257844585173314736547514473264437245",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbw",
    "size": 8
  },
  "156": {
    "question": "463352241531125643113433524416251362",
    "answer": "wwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "157": {
    "question": "132526621445153462562114435611244451",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwbww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "158": {
    "question": "241236524361355123315345334412261433",
    "answer": "bwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwbbwbwwwwwwbwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "159": {
    "question": "2336647765472648214277151768356454854621856243174673581272147323",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "160": {
    "question": "453633546512235461135224224435513321",
    "answer": "wwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "161": {
    "question": "551336165213211524543163644515235655",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "162": {
    "question": "2344133514213453513314251",
    "answer": "bwwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwwwwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "163": {
    "question": "1242441332224412514452213",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwbwww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "164": {
    "question": "3123532251334321522444131",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "165": {
    "question": "4453154243143221325435411",
    "answer": "wbwwwwwwbwwbwwbbwbwwwwwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "166": {
    "question": "515331613512251311132364364123321351",
    "answer": "bwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "167": {
    "question": "5471563351672226272485654364215766136832823467147642148718662422",
    "answer": "bwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "168": {
    "question": "224133654513322463464332513241236122",
    "answer": "bwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "169": {
    "question": "512241141265132614645134261423154321",
    "answer": "wwwbwbbwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "170": {
    "question": "3435112544311454212413412",
    "answer": "bwwwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbbwwww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "171": {
    "question": "114243352311213456236221545622324163",
    "answer": "bwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "172": {
    "question": "326534351532614525244263432116162412",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "173": {
    "question": "6434528272563318136841724821145651652642864557235712173734538562",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbbwwwwbww",
    "size": 8
  },
  "174": {
    "question": "4425451442144342341542122",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "175": {
    "question": "1342341354325423523152441",
    "answer": "wbwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwbwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "176": {
    "question": "2533121235131244235344412",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbbwbww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "177": {
    "question": "541216452345164425651452335241326154",
    "answer": "wwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwwbw",
    "size": 6
  },
  "178": {
    "question": "651144416532413146235165442653365225",
    "answer": "wwwbwbbwwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbbwwwwwwwbwbw",
    "size": 6
  },
  "179": {
    "question": "3511213253242351254453323",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "180": {
    "question": "5137441417143468687361336681571575261346367225674563547223477852",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "181": {
    "question": "513461352144215414461525524453614531",
    "answer": "wbwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwbbwbwwwwwwbwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "182": {
    "question": "554614163425433511631432412155151264",
    "answer": "wbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbbwbwww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "183": {
    "question": "135452551524523214462151326541315635",
    "answer": "wwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwbbwbwww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "184": {
    "question": "7154153445372781245855746781443383437215617763783614865513754762",
    "answer": "wbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbww",
    "size": 8
  },
  "185": {
    "question": "4324445321132452421351131",
    "answer": "bwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "186": {
    "question": "7634135815647363527581143441258228553761318716416418231515534846",
    "answer": "wwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbw",
    "size": 8
  },
  "187": {
    "question": "531325125534515432563331154212241153",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "188": {
    "question": "554136241652163515632425536321114562",
    "answer": "bwbwwwwwwwwbbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "189": {
    "question": "2278331566421713562422718253212621666487738161422417584117624238",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbww",
    "size": 8
  },
  "190": {
    "question": "331213153362512642634521242316226635",
    "answer": "bwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwbww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "191": {
    "question": "7861347253367387751286357185435186656714127436186548714327536825",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "192": {
    "question": "7155832578621734621471638521651173766268276346514635218761473575",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "193": {
    "question": "351652246314413364543546164254615231",
    "answer": "wwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwbww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "194": {
    "question": "241131235141451364426114641253263123",
    "answer": "bwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "195": {
    "question": "552154614425154155256341441512343316",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwbww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "196": {
    "question": "643221561352352256125633442253234165",
    "answer": "wbwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbbwbwbwwwwwww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "197": {
    "question": "215135634452113456415263561425251641",
    "answer": "wbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwbbwbwww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "198": {
    "question": "4233545121212522432123212",
    "answer": "bwbwwwwwwbbwbwwwwwbwbwwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "199": {
    "question": "261142424256142563551652631621526314",
    "answer": "wwbwwbbwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "200": {
    "question": "654143226545543414231654132433515362",
    "answer": "wwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwbbwwwww",
    "size": 6
  }
}